What would home look like?
I don't know.
A farmhouse in the
valley, I guess,
like the one we grew
up in, Liza and I.
I remember hiding in
the orchard at night.
Looking down at the
lighted windows,
waiting for our daddy
to fall asleep,
just so we could
go back inside.
Do you remember that, Liza?
Hmm? Do you remember that?
I'd imagine him passing out.
With one of his lucky
strikes in his hand,
the house catching fire,
the orchard, the whole
valley burning up.
So, how does it feel, Liza?
Your first big score?
I don't know. Excited, nervous,
like I'm spying on someone,
someone doing something dirty.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
Shame.
It's all right, little sis.
It's a good sign when
you feel a little bad.
Liza? Liza, can you hear me?
Liza?
I can hear you.
Are you in pain?
No. I think I'm all right.
Theo?
Theo should've worn his safety belt.
Shit.
Liza, can you move?
I think so.
Then be ready to.
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Sir, I hope you can forgive me.
Addison?
Liza, get the money.
Liza, now!
See if you can get to your bag.
Get anything warm.
I'm sure that officer called for
backup, at least an ambulance.
We can't be foolish
now, you understand?
You have the money?
Mm-hmm. Most of it.
You have your health?
I think so.
Let's not dally.
Mills!
Let's go. Pack it up.
You're out of here.
You got your papers?
You know how to get your
car out of impound?
I'm okay. Thanks.
Going home to see your
folks for Thanksgiving?
I don't know.
Just let me out of here.
Hello?
Dad, it's Jay.
Dad, are you there?
Hello, son.
How you've been?
Decent.
Listen, I'm in the
middle of something.
I'll get your mother.
Who is it?
Hello?
Mom, it's me.
Oh! Oh, my goodness. Hi, honey!
How are you?
I'm out.
What?
This morning. Good behavior.
Oh, my God. That's wonderful.
Then you'll be here for
Thanksgiving tomorrow?
Oh! I'll make it nice, honey,
just the way it used to be.
How about dad?
Your father loves you, Jay.
He just has a hard
time showing it.
Listen. If it's more
comfortable tomorrow morning,
he'll be gone hunting.
We could talk about it then.
I just need the keys to the
cottage, if that's okay.
Oh, sure. They're here.
Just come and get 'em.
Do you need money?
Are you in trouble?
Mom I've got to go.
Read the sign!
Oh, shit.
Jay.
"Mohawk" mills.
Just Jay.
Time really flies by.
It didn't fly by for me.
Well, come on in, kid.
Just watching some
tape on a new fighter.
Yeah, you were really
something then.
No one threw a
left hook harder.
You weren't even there, Ronnie.
How'd you end up with my medal?
I just figured I'd hang
onto it, you know,
for safekeeping.
Right.
It looks good on you, kid.
When did you get out?
Couple of hours ago.
Wow, you came straight here.
I'm honored.
Who tipped off the boxing
commission, Ronnie?
Hell if I know.
Well, how come I was the
only one that took the fall?
How come you were
never indicted?
A lot of questions.
I had a lot of time
to think of them.
I want the money you owe me.
How do you figure I
owe you money, kid?
The fucking fight, Ronnie!
Okay, I get it.
Remember, kid,
you were like a son to me.
I don't have a lot right now,
but I've got some.
Some's better than none, right?
Not much, but it's all
I've got right now.
Are you fucking stupid? You think you
can come in here and make demands?
You're on parole! You
don't dare touch me.
You could've been a
great fucking loser!
We could've made a lot
of money together.
See, the way I
figure, you owe me.
Ronnie.
Oh, Jesus.
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
Hello?
9-1-1.
Is anybody there?
Stay on the line with
me if you can hear me.
We'll dispatch a car
to this address.
Jay? Hey, man!
Long time no see!
Hey. Sorry, man.
Jay? Hey! What's the problem?
Watch it, man!
I told Jay to stop
by tomorrow morning.
I see.
Don't do this, Chet.
It's not fair.
He turned his back
on his family.
I wonder who that is.
Hi, Hanna!
Hi! Hi, sheriff mills.
Not me. My spurs are hung. Oh!
It's so good to see you guys.
Seems like it's been forever.
Look at you.
What a pretty young
woman you turned into.
You're the spitting
image of your mom.
I remember my mom and dad
used to take me here.
For Thanksgiving
when I was little.
Jay and I used to always
feed all those leftover.
Bones and things to that
big pig you guys had.
Jay was always
going on about...
Oh, uh, what brings
you out here now?
Oh, uh, we actually
have a bad situation.
I wanted to give you
guys a heads up.
What do you mean by bad?
Late last night, one
of the tribal casinos.
Down in mt. Pleasant
was robbed.
Two armed suspects
wearing masks...
Anyone hurt?
Around 6 this morning, a
state trooper came upon.
An accident site a
ways South of us.
When backup arrived, they found
the trooper shot to death.
Oh, my God.
One of the suspects
died in the crash.
At least one more took to
the national forest here.
We're setting up roadblocks
and sending in search teams,
but it is possible he
could slip through,
so we're just letting all
the families out here know.
Well, it's a huge area.
He'd never make it this
far north on foot.
And the temperature's
supposed to keep dropping.
I heard blizzard conditions.
I'd say let him
freeze to death.
Coyotes will find him.
What are you looking
at, Addison?
Pardon me.
It's okay to look.
Hush! The devil will hear you.
What did I promise you
when we started this?
That no one would get hurt.
Well, I want you
to remember this.
You didn't hurt anyone.
I made the choice, and now
things are different.
Different how?
We're going to split up.
They don't know
anything about you.
You were just the distraction.
I don't like this plan.
I didn't ask you
if you liked it.
We shouldn't split up! Shh!
Listen.
You follow that path and
then cut toward the road.
Use your wits. Hitch a ride.
Keep heading north.
We can still make it to
Canada, but till then,
you don't know me anymore.
I'm not your brother anymore,
not until I let you
know it's okay.
Remember how I taught you?
Leave your phone on,
and I'll call you
tonight, okay?
You're my little girl. Say it.
I'm your little girl.
That's good.
Here you go.
What if you don't call?
Well, then I'm dead.
So do you have any plans
for Thanksgiving?
No, just dinner. How about you?
Any news from your mom, Hanna?
You?
No, sweetie. Not
in a long time.
Well, it was really
good to see you.
Bye. Bye.
Oh, you should stop by
tomorrow for dinner.
Oh, thanks. You know,
I was going to ask my dad
if he had any plans,
see if he wanted to do
something together.
Okay. Bye.
Hey, Doris! What's the word?
The word is shit,
and there's a big pile of it
waiting for you in the office.
Becker? And the boys.
Any mail come for me? A letter?
Didn't come in yet.
Well, let me know. Yes, ma'am.
We'll provide manpower and
additional search support,
along with the other counties.
Shut the fucking door, eh?
State k-9 teams won't be
here till late tonight,
so we're going in this
afternoon with my dogs.
Use your radios, use your heads.
Everybody wears their vests.
If you come upon this
guy, call it in.
We all want to make it
home for Turkey dinner.
Well, if you keep talking,
I'm not going to make
it for Turkey dinner.
Travis, this morning
while you were fucking.
That little rat
you call a wife,
this guy shot a
cop in the face.
The cop's name was
Alan townsend.
He served as a trooper
for 18 years.
That man is dead, gone forever.
All right. Take it easy. Sorry.
This is the real deal, boys.
You understand?
All right, now listen up.
Here's what we're going to do.
Travis, Brice, bill, you'll
be with me heading west.
From the accident site
toward the Lake Shore.
The other four of you
will be led by Denny.
You'll head east toward I-75.
Okay? Let's get going.
What about me?
What about you?
What team am I with?
None.
What do you mean?
I mean you ain't going out.
You can't do that.
I'm responsible for
these men's lives.
I'll do what the
hell I see fit.
Besides, what if you got out there,
and something major happened,
like you had to
change your tampon?
No offense, deputy.
Then I'd change it, dad.
Shit.
Shit!
Miss. Miss, are you okay?
Hey, hey.
Are you all right?
Come on!
Ah, you no good mule!
Start, God damn you!
You rotten old pile of shit!
Ha!
I have a past wife that
comes to me in dreams.
She told me you'd be coming.
You can barely see
anything out there.
Yeah. It's going
into white-out.
What?
When you can't see what's
right in front of you.
My car broke down. I got lost.
You live around here?
My folks. They live
close to the border.
I'm just passing through.
You think you could
give me a lift?
No.
I'm sorry. I can't.
I'll drop you at the next
gas station, all right?
This is kind of like an old
movie, don't you think?
What is?
Us. Two people meeting
in a snowstorm.
I guess.
What's your name?
What do you want it to be?
Come on. Didn't you ever play
pretend when you were a kid?
We're strangers. We can
be whoever we want.
So, who am I?
Come on. Give me a name.
Look, I'm sorry. I
really don't...
Shh. Name me.
Patricia.
I like that.
Patricia. The bad girl.
The FBI academy!
You passed the exam!
I'm so damn proud
of you, honey.
Yeah.
What? I don't know.
Hanna, you're going
to be an FBI agent.
You're finally going to
leave this shit hole.
Turn around and look at me.
He's a son of a bitch, Hanna.
Who? Who do you think?
The sheriff, your dad!
He's not that bad.
He doesn't really
mean it, you know?
It's just been hard for him
since my mom took off.
That was years ago, Hanna.
You're not actually
considering giving this up?
Why?
So you can take care of him?
I'm all he's got left.
This is from my heart, honey.
This is your life,
and you only get one.
Well, good luck.
Thanks for rescuing me.
Hey, folks. Just
to let you know,
state police were just here.
They're closing the road.
Are you serious?
Full on blizzard.
Plows can't get through
till the morning.
So, batten down the hatches
and pull up a stool.
You're probably going
to be here all night.
I know I will.
Got a phone?
Oh, yeah. Pay phone's
in back by the can.
Hey, it's me.
I'm at this place.
I'm stuck here for the night.
There's this guy. He's
the perfect ride.
His parents have a
place near the border.
I'm going to get him
to take me there.
The address is 207.
Old mills farm road, bear lake.
Can you make it there?
I hope you're okay.
Okay. Bye.
Hey. Can I get you a drink?
I'm okay.
Ah, first one's on me. Call
it a snowstorm special.
You and your wife?
Oh, we'd love a drink.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
My name's Patricia.
This is my husband Addison.
Addison? That's a funny one.
It's his daddy's name.
You two married long?
No. We're pretty new at it.
Ah, thought so.
Still got the glow.
Well, my name's Mandy,
and this is my bar.
Got it in the divorce.
Never used to come in here
when he ran the place,
- but now I love it.
- Hey, Mandy!
How about bringing us
some more pitchers, huh?
My ex-sister-in-law, tricia.
Listen, honey. You
can pick the guy.
You just can't pick the family.
Come here!
Come to mommy! Come here!
Lisa, get back here!
No!
Come here, baby! Come here!
Lisa, get your ass
back in the cabin.
If you know what's
good for you!
No! That goes for
your mother, too,
or I'll be hunting more
than deer tomorrow!
You're not going anywhere!
There's nothing for Miles!
That baby's going to freeze!
I'll be waiting!
Don't you move.
Take your coat and go outside.
Who are you... shut your mouth!
Liza, get outside now.
Her name's Lisa.
She only does what I tell her.
You'll be dead before
your hand touches it.
Lisa, your mom's up on
the hill with the baby.
She's very cold, and
she needs your help.
You need to take her
something warm.
You stay right there, Lisa.
He ain't got the guts to
do it in front of you.
Probably wouldn't be
good for a little girl,
seeing her stepfather killed.
Later in life, I mean.
I want my mom.
She's up on the
hill with the baby.
You're fucking my
wife, is that it?
Lisa, leave now.
Is that who you are, huh?
I knew it. I fucking knew it!
Go ahead! You can have her,
the little fucking slut!
Fuck you!
Fuck you...
So, tell me something
about you, Addison.
What do you want to know?
I don't know.
What do you do for a living?
Why are you always so serious?
Anything.
I was a boxer,
but it seems like a
long time ago now.
Like a boxer in
the ring, boxer?
Yeah, my dad trained
me since I was a kid.
Got me all the way to
the Beijing games.
Oh, you must have
been really good.
I won the silver medal.
Is that it?
You have it on you?
I don't usually, but I
happen to be today.
Can I...
That is really cool.
It ain't the gold, but...
It's amazing.
I've never been
good at anything.
Here we go. You're
going to have to help.
Carry the baby.
This boy needs you, okay?
He can't make it without you.
Here you go.
Lisa, you can help
your mom and the baby.
By getting in here.
And getting under the
covers and cuddling up.
There you go.
Cuddle up real tight,
while I have a think
for a minute.
You know what, Lisa,
I'm trying to imagine
how you must feel.
I think it would be a
complicated feeling.
I guess, right now, nothing in
the whole world seems safe.
Your step-daddy's gone.
Your mom's sick.
And you're in the
forest with a stranger.
What happened to your hand?
Well, I got into a fight.
With a great Indian chief.
He cut my finger off.
Did you kill him?
Yes, I did.
Are you going to kill me?
No.
You're a child.
Children should be protected.
Angels protect me.
Maybe that's how you
should think of me.
I'm like an angel come
down from the storm.
To remove that man
from your life.
Once you're up at this
cottage of yours.
All by your lonesome,
what then?
I don't know.
I just need to think
for a while, you know?
I couldn't stand that.
I hate being alone. It
scares me, always has.
If you still want it,
I'll give you a
lift to the border.
I wish you hadn't
stopped for me.
I wish somebody else
had come along.
I wish I was somebody else.
Just pretend, okay?
I'm not pretending.
Fuck me, Addison.
So, what do you want to
be when you grow up?
A nurse.
Grandma Vicky is a nurse.
I always wanted to be a farmer.
We had a fruit farm,
peaches mostly.
My daddy was a drunk, and
he ran it into the ground.
When I was a kid, I always
wanted to fix it up...
And farm it just right.
Can I change the baby?
Yeah.
Hey, it's me.
I'm at this place. I'm
stuck here for the night.
There's this guy. He's
the perfect ride.
His family lives
near the border.
I'm going to get him
to take me there.
The address is 207 old mills
farm road, bear lake.
You'll make a great nurse.
I have a baby sister.
When we were kids,
I used to take care of
her, just like you are.
Where is she now?
She's out there somewhere.
I think you should leave
your sister alone.
It's about Amy, my daughter.
You know her.
Sure. She was a couple of years
ahead of me at school, but sure.
Please.
Then you know she's
always been afraid.
To be without a
man in her life.
It's probably because of her dad and I.
We never...
Mrs. woodward, tell
me what happened.
She didn't come
home last night.
She was supposed to
come to my house...
She and the kids and
her husband Bobby.
He's a horrible man.
A violent man. Do you know him?
We've had calls to their
house on a few occasions.
Well, she was going to ask
him for a divorce yesterday.
Did you try calling?
No. They were at
Bobby's hunting cabin.
There's no phone there.
There's no nothing, and
it's out in the woods.
Could you please check on her?
Make sure, just tell me
everything's all right.
Make me feel like a
silly old mother.
Sure.
I'll be home around noon,
unless I'm tracking one.
Hey.
Yeah?
You've been pretty quiet this morning.
You okay?
Yeah.
You know, parenting isn't
easy, Chet, not for anyone.
You make it look that way.
Well, just because I'm better
at hiding the hard parts.
And you're always graceful.
In case you get hungry.
I thought you said
your spurs were hung.
It's better to
have and not need.
Okay then.
Stay warm.
Don't tell me what to do.
It's getting light out.
Where are you?
Are you still alive?
I think I'd feel
it if you died.
I mean, at least
I think I would.
I feel like I just
have to keep moving.
Addison?
Everything's just...
Everything's getting
so confusing.
That guy I told you about,
he turned out to be a real jerk.
He just disappeared on me, so...
I'll find another way,
and I'll call you.
Or you call me. Where are you?
Okay. Bye.
Hey! Hey!
Hey, buddy. What's
your problem?
I'll put you in a fucking coma!
Drive the fuck away!
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Last night was fun
and all, but...
But what?
Well, it was just a game!
That is bullshit,
and you know it.
Do I? You don't
even know my name.
So, tell me!
What does it matter? I
could've been anybody.
It matters to me.
Why are you doing this?
Hey, bill.
You order breakfast?
Come on, Travis.
What are you doing here, Hanna?
Becker will have your head.
Vicky woodward is worried
about her daughter.
Their cabin's a couple
of Miles from here.
Where's Becker?
Headed north about an hour ago.
To meet with the state police.
You want us to come with you?
Not necessary.
No, it probably is.
When I was 10, I watched
my father bleed to death.
In the weeds beside our house.
He pulled himself across
the yard with his arms,
screamed at me,
and then he died.
Someone shot him.
Want to know what I did next?
Washed him off with
the garden hose,
combed his hair,
sat beside him and waited
for someone to find me.
Who found you?
My brother.
He turned off the hose
and took me for a walk.
What happened then?
A lot of strangers at our
house, a lot of cops.
People trying to figure
out where to put me.
My father was a monster.
An animal, and he
died like one.
I'm supposed to be a grownup.
If I was someone else,
I could have a
husband of my own...
Having my own babies.
Instead I'm all messed up.
Liza...
My name is Liza.
I'm Jay.
What's the matter, Hanna?
Why are we stopping?
Guys, it looks like
this was left here.
Strange, huh?
So what?
Becker, do you copy? Hey,
hey, what are you doing?
I'm calling in to
Becker for backup.
Call in what? It's a snowmobile
and a hunting cabin.
While the two of you
have your little spat,
I'm just going to
go and do my job.
We have to check it out.
Okay, fine. So we check it out,
but don't go calling
Becker now for nothing.
Me and Brice are the ones who
will end up in deep shit.
Becker told us to call.
I'm calling.
Becker, do you copy?
What the hell? You
can't do that!
Can't do what?
Such an asshole.
Hello! Bobby?
Hello!
This is the sheriff's office.
You're going to get
us in trouble, Hanna.
I know it's early.
We'd just like to
have a quick word.
Oh, my God.
Hello!
Brice! Get away! It's him!
Brice?
You're no angel at all.
No, I am not.
Brice, you all right?
Hanna, get down!
Come on!
Oh, fuck!
Are you all right?
You're not even supposed
to be here, Hanna!
God damn it, Travis!
Travis!
You know, this is
my first snowman?
You're shitting me.
Not a lot of snow in Alabama.
One night when I was a kid,
the northern lights were out,
and my dad and I made these
snowmen out in the pasture.
Like a boxing match,
two snow fighters
throwing punches.
I remember I didn't want
to go to bed that night.
My dad carried me all the
way back to the house.
When I got down off the
podium in Beijing,
he was so fucking proud of me.
And then later in
the dressing room,
I told him I was leaving
home to go pro.
I said to him...
I said if I had a real coach,
maybe I'd won the gold.
He still love you?
Yeah, I guess, but...
Well, you're lucky.
You should see him.
If I was going to see him,
I'd like to introduce you.
It's Thanksgiving. That's
standard procedure.
You don't want me
there, Jay, seriously.
I seriously do.
What about Patricia? Isn't
she going to be there?
Who?
Now, don't tell me
there's no Patricia.
Who is she to you?
I'd rather not talk about her.
It's kind of personal.
I think I've told you some
personal things, Jay.
Miss December.
What?
Patricia is miss December.
Playboy, Christmas issue.
She's a centerfold?
A nudie picture?
Did you two have a
meaningful relationship?
We did. She was
very understanding,
not too demanding.
And were you faithful
to her, Jay?
I was. She was my one and only.
She never let me down.
Hey, lovebirds!
Roads are open!
And to answer your question,
she probably won't be.
At Thanksgiving dinner
at my parents' house.
Good. Bitch better stay clear.
Guys!
Dad, I think I shot him.
I think he's wounded.
He's wearing a buckskin jacket.
With a blackbird or an eagle...
At least I think it's
an eagle on the back...
Just shut your mouth.
Dad! I said shut your mouth!
I told you to stay
out of the woods!
You see what happens when
you stick your nose in?
People start dying!
Where's Travis?
A field, about 10 Miles west.
He's dead?
If you were one of my boys,
I would hit you
so fucking hard.
If I were one of your boys,
you'd be proud of me.
I want everybody the
hell out of here.
All of you. You hear me?
Well, I can help... all of you!
Shut up!
Chester mills, you'd
better not be.
Walking in here
with your boots...
Shh.
What's your name?
June.
June, put that pan
down, please.
Is there anyone else
in the house, June?
No.
Step down and take a seat.
Who might come home, June?
My husband, Chet.
Where is he?
Deer hunting.
He'll be armed?
With a rifle.
Why are you so calm?
A panicking woman is
no help to anyone.
I like you, June.
You do as I say, and I won't
hurt you or your family.
Thank you.
Would you mind op...
Opening a window, please?
May I take a look at that?
Are you my mother?
Somebody's mother.
Ah, shit!
You'll live.
Well, that remains to
be determined, June,
but thank you.
Do not turn around.
Do exactly what I say.
Slowly put your hands on your
head, interlocking your fingers.
To do that, I'd have
to take my hand.
Off the gun I have pointed
at June on the table...
Which isn't going to happen.
He will shoot you, kiddo.
I don't think he will.
Don't try me, son.
No. He has too much to lose.
Sir, believe me when I say
that I genuinely like June.
So, for both of us, would
you please back down?
God damn it.
Open the rifle action and
put the gun on the floor.
Take a seat beside your wife.
I'm sorry.
Nothing to be sorry for.
Chet, is it? How
was the hunting?
You know, when I was a kid, we
had a Springfield 20 gauge.
We used to hunt
ducks and coons.
You bake pies from
scratch, June?
For Thanksgiving, I do.
Oh, that's right.
It's Thanksgiving.
Would it be all right.
If we went ahead
and served dinner?
It would be really nice
to have a good meal.
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
I would like that.
Honey...
Chet, we have to eat.
It will occupy us.
Keep things from
getting too crazy.
Thank you, June.
Don't thank me. Chet
shot the goose.
Well, thank you, Chet.
What are you looking for?
Nothing. I'm just, uh...
Wondering if the police
are waiting for you?
I know what people are like
when they're on the run.
I fucked up.
It wasn't my fault, but...
I'm not going back to prison.
I can't.
Is it safe?
Who's that, June?
Oh, my God. It's our son.
It's Jay.
Well, well, well.
Be careful. The steps are icy.
Hey, mom.
Jay. Oh, Jay.
I brought a guest.
Oh, Jay. Listen to me.
There's a man in our
house, and he has a gun.
Don't. Don't do anything.
He'll hurt your dad.
Please just come
in, both of you.
Dad, you okay?
I'm okay, son.
Good afternoon.
You must be Jay.
What do you want?
This must be your wife.
She's my friend.
Well, I think the lady
can speak for herself.
What's your name?
Liza.
Well, that's a nice name.
Take a seat.
Both of you.
The goose should be done soon.
Is that correct, June? Yes.
Great. I don't know about
you all, but I'm famished.
Chet, here.
Have some wine. Take
it away from me.
It's going straight to my head.
I need some food, and
I need some sleep.
Besides, it's Thanksgiving.
Are you testing me, Jay?
Because that would
be a terrible idea.
This is sheriff t. Becker,
requesting the state
police crime scene unit...
And be advised we're
losing daylight.
And must stay on the
suspect's trail.
Happy Thanksgiving, mom.
Hello.
Yeah, this is the sheriff's office.
Hanna Becker speaking.
Sure.
Detective Frank Mac,
Detroit police department.
Say that again?
Oh, yeah. I know the family.
I know where they live.
A concussion? So you
need his statement.
Got it.
I'll go over there.
I'll let you know.
Happy holiday to you, too.
Jesus Christ.
June, do you say grace
at Thanksgiving?
We give thanks.
And how does that work?
We all go around and say
something we're thankful for.
An excellent idea.
Would you mind starting?
Please?
I'm thankful for this food,
for God's charity,
and for giving me his
two greatest men,
my husband and my son.
Well said.
Chet? You're next.
I'm thankful for June,
the love of my life.
Wow, that was sweet, Chet!
How about your son?
What's wrong with him, hmm?
Let's ask him.
Jay, what are you grateful for?
It's none of your
fucking business.
No, you're missing
the point, Jay.
Well, I'm not going
to give you anything.
Jay, it's your turn.
Addison, please stop.
These people haven't
done anything to you.
You best watch your
mouth, little girl.
Don't you forget
where you belong.
Give thanks, Jay.
You'd better say something
I know you really mean.
You think I'm afraid of you?
Look at you.
You're nothing
without that gun.
What if this is your daddy's
last moment of life?
What do you want him
to take with him?
Jay. Please, honey.
I'm sorry, dad.
I messed everything up so bad.
That fight, they told
me it was the only way.
They'd give me a
shot at the title.
I laid down.
I let 'em beat me.
I don't deserve to be
sitting here at your table.
This is your table, son.
And you're not the only
one who messed up.
Once again, June,
the goose was really
quite wonderful.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to have
some more red wine.
I'm going to have some more
of your wife's homemade pie.
About the police?
I don't know, Chet.
I feel pretty good
just sitting here.
Hey, it's Hanna.
Hanna Becker.
We know that officer.
She's a friend of the family.
Just dropping by
on Thanksgiving?
I invited her.
That slip your mind, June?
Ask her in.
No.
Do it.
Come on in, Hanna.
Hey, everybody.
Sorry to interrupt.
I don't think you know everyone.
This is...
I'm the killer.
I'm the one you're
all looking for.
I'm sorry, Hanna.
I didn't know what to do.
I wouldn't either.
Give me your belt.
Take a seat.
Go on.
June, would you please
serve some pie?
Do you want pumpkin or apple?
I'm going to have pumpkin.
Seems more appropriate
for the holidays.
So, Hanna, what are you doing here?
Thank you.
It's Thanksgiving.
Don't you got anybody
of your own?
I'm here for Jay.
Hey. Long time.
Yeah.
I got a call from a
detective in Detroit.
He needs to talk with you.
Oops. In trouble with
the police, Jay?
That's kind of embarrassing
for your folks.
I mean, this all seems
pretty wholesome.
What went wrong, buddy?
What are they after you for?
I'm dying to know.
I have something I'd
like to give thanks for.
What's that?
My brother.
Why?
Because when we were
little, he protected me.
When I couldn't protect myself.
I was so young.
He thinks I can't remember,
but I remember all of it.
The sound of the gun,
the blood on my shoe.
My brother killed the devil.
He saved me from hell, and
I am forever thankful.
I love him so much for it.
But now, I need a chance.
I need a chance at my own life,
and I want my
brother's blessing.
I need him to please let me go.
Eat.
Eat!
You two in love?
You think he loves you?
Do you think he loves you?
Look at me.
Look at me!
Don't fucking touch her! Sit!
You put your hand on the
table where I can see it.
Stop it! Stop it!
Sit down! Sit, June, sit!
God damn you to hell.
Addison, please. Come on.
Let's just go, just you and me.
No, baby. Come on. Let's go right now.
Come on.
We're way past that now.
I'm your little girl.
No. Please.
Did you fuck her, Jay? Did you?
You think he cares about you?
You look at your boyfriend now.
Look at him!
Please, God, no! You
look at your family.
You look what you've done! Huh?
This is sheriff t. Becker
requesting immediate backup.
I'm going into the old mills farm,
mills farm road off county line 55.
Possible manhunt
suspect on premises,
described as wearing
a deerskin jacket.
With eagle emblem,
possibly wounded.
Copy that. Units en route.
Be advised not to
engage until backup...
Daddy! The living room.
Happy Thanksgiving.
I'm glad you could make it.
Please don't!
No!
Jay!
Please! Please.
He's my brother.
Do you love her, Jay?
Yes, I do.
Addison...
Get him out of here!
Ma'am, I need you to get back.
Please. I need you to get back.
Ma'am...
Get an ambulance!
Come on. That's it.
That other officer, the
sheriff, wasn't wearing a vest.
He's in rough shape.
Do you know who his
next of kin is?
What would heaven look like?
I don't know.
A farmhouse in the
valley, I guess,
like the one we grew
up in, Liza and I.